vosizneias.com 2018-12-28

# Vos Iz Neias (VIN News) » Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the vosizneias.com and VosIzNeias and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to VosIzNeias include vosizneias.com and VIN News. The VIN News website is a News and Information site. By using the VIN News website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**  
VIN News may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by VIN News. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the VIN News website.

VIN News encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from VIN News so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. VIN News is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the VIN News website.

**Use of Your Personal Information**  
VIN News collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

VIN News may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from VIN News and its affiliates. VIN News may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

**VIN News does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.**

VIN News may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to VIN News, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

VIN News may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within VIN News, in order to determine what VIN News services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within VIN News to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

VIN News will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on VIN News or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of VIN News; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of VIN News, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**  
The VIN News website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A  
cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize VIN News pages, or register with VIN News site or services, a cookie helps VIN News to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same VIN News website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the VIN News features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the VIN News services or websites you visit.

**Security of Your Personal Information**  
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
VIN News does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Disconnecting Your VIN News Account from Third Party Websites**  
You will be able to connect your VIN News account to third party accounts.  
BY CONNECTING YOUR VIN NEWS ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES).

IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE.  
You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from VIN News by contacting us here:

\- Web page: vosizneias.com  
\- Email: vinnews@vosizneias.com

**Changes to this Statement**  
VIN News will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. VIN News encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how VIN News is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
VIN News welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that VIN News has not adhered to this Statement, please contact VIN News at: vinnews@vosizneias.com

_________________

Effective as of May 19, 2013
